Introduction
Chapter 1 Building on a Foundation of Long-Term Thinking
Chapter 2 Creating Flow and Eliminating Waste in Every Process
Chapter 3 Standardizing Work and Empowering People
Chapter 4 Building a Culture of Problem Solving and Continuous Improvement
Chapter 5 Respecting People and Developing Leaders
Chapter 6 Making Decisions Slowly by Consensus, Implementing Rapidly
Chapter 7 Going to the Source: Genchi Genbutsu
Chapter 8 Developing Exceptional People and Teams
Chapter 9 Respecting and Challenging Partners and Suppliers
Chapter 10 Using Technology Thoughtfully
Chapter 11 Becoming a Learning Organization
Chapter 12 Building Quality into Every Step
Chapter 13 Visual Management and Transparency
Chapter 14 Sustaining the Culture: Leadership as Stewards
Conclusion